SANAZ ZERAATI

Front-End Developer(React JS)

ABOUT ME

A self-taught front-end developer for a year and a mature person with more than 5 years of experience with an engineering background as a GIS technician and control project manager. During this time, I realized my interest in web development and decided to enter the profession resolutely as a front-end developer with a HackYourFuture course and other educational resources.

I am a highly enthused, responsible, motivated, hardworking, and reliable person. I have experience working as part of a team and individually and extremely driven, with a clear goal to succeed. Hence, I am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills as a Front-End Developer in your company.

CONTACT

- szeraati69@gmail.com
- sanaz-zeraati.ir
- linkedin.com/in/sanaz-zeraati
- github.com/sanaz-git
- +98 914 056 7100

LANGUAGE

English (Advance) German (Basic) Persian (Native)

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Hiking, Climbing, Traveling, Music

SKILS

- HTML&CSS
- Javascript
- React.js (hooks)
- REST api
- MaterialUI
- SASS
- Git
- BootStrap

PROJECTS

• Shopping Cart - Link

React|Context|useReducer|useParams|Rout

• Login form - Link

React|Context|Rout

- Crypto Link
- Credit Card Validator Link

React | useState

• Weather App - Link

React|useState|useParams|Charts|Rout

• responsive-website - Link

Vanila JavaScrips

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Hamyar System Company

June 2022 - September 2022 - Kerman

React | Material-UI | Sass | AG GRID

HACKYOURFUTURE CURRICULUM - Link

June 2021 - June 2022 - SelfStudy Web Development Program

PROJECT CONTROL MANAGER

Water & Waste Water Company

September 2019 - Present

GIS SPECIALIST

Water & Waste Water Company

January 2017 - September 2019

EDUCATION

MASTER OF SCIENCE WATER RESOURCE ENGINEERING

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman, Iran

September 2013 - September 2016

Operation Evaluation of Copula Function in Flood Frequency Analysis

BACHELOR OF WATER ENGINEERING

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman, Iran

September 2009- September 2013

Mapping underground Dam in Arid and Semi-Arid Area